// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Yuvraj Singh scored his first one-day century against",
    answer: "Bangladesh",
    options: [
     "Bangladesh",
     "Sri Lanka",
     "Australia",
     "New Zealand"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which Indian batsman has scored double century in ODI cricket match",
    answer: "Rohit Sharma",
    options: [
     "Virat Kohli",
     "Rohit Sharma",
     "Kl Rahul",
     "Suresh Raina"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "India won T20I world cup in which year",
    answer: "2007",
    options: [
     "2008",
     "2016",
     "2007",
     "2011"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the fastest Indian bowler to reach 100 wickets in One-day internationals.",
    answer: "Ajit Agarkar",
    options: [
     "Kapil dev",
     "Anil Kumble",
     "Ajit Agarkar",
     "Zaheer Khan"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many players in the ground in cricket at a time",
    answer: "11",
    options: [
      "11",
      "12",
      "10",
      "15"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " What is color of ball used in limited over match ?",
    answer: "White",
    options: [
      "Green",
      "White",
      "Red",
      "Pink"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Who among the following introduced the world to One-Day Internationals?",
    answer: "Kerry Packer",
    options: [
     "Kerry Packer",
     "Len Hutton",
     "Frank Worrell",
     "Thomas Hughes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who was the captian of Indian Cricket team when India has won ODI cricket world cup",
    answer: "MS Dhoni",
    options: [
     "Virat Kohli",
     "Rohit Sharma",
     "MS Dhoni",
     "Rahul Dravid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "International cricket is not played using which of the following balls",
    answer: "Blue",
    options: [
      "White ball",
      "Red ball",
      "Pink ball",
      "Blue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is the oldest test cricket playing country in the world",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
     "Australia",
     "India",
     "West Indies",
     "South Africa"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Where is the headquarter of the ICC?",
    answer: "Dubai",
    options: [
      "London",
      "Cape Town",
      "Sydney",
      "Dubai"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following international competition is not organized by the ICC",
    answer: "Syed Mushtaq Ali Trophy",
    options: [
      "Champions Trophy",
      "World Cricket League",
      " Under-19 Cricket World Cup",
      "Syed Mushtaq Ali Trophy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is chosen at the ICC men's cricketer of the year 2017",
    answer: "Virat Kohli",
    options: [
      "K.L. Rahul",
      "Virat Kohli",
      "Steve Smith",
      "Rohit Sharma"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: " When was the first Cricket World Cup held?",
    answer: "1975",
    options: [
      "1975",
      "1957",
      "1987",
      "1929"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which nation has won 2022 T20I World Title",
    answer: "England",
    options: [
     "India",
     "England",
     "South Africa",
     "Australia",
    ]
  },

  


  

  

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];